These players are legendary when it comes to the one v five s
I miss you go go go start gun
Shot it
Shock it
Let it go
One enemy remaining here
We go
Holy icicle one v five
Baby icicle for one v five
Really set the tone for the whole match
From that point forward
I'm your host
Awesome joey
Be sure to like
Subscribe and comment for a shot at a hundred dollar
Giveaway via paypal
And then let's get right back to it
Oh my god
One enemy remaining
Ninety nine
We have a five one enemy remaining
A talk about a post plant performance that was insane
It's crazy how useful the cipher can be in those situations
Information is everything
One enemy remaining
Oh
My gosh
Their crosshair placement and steadiness is on real life
I've had a lot of players wish they could be this calm in these situations
Just take it
Too late
One enemy remaining
Let's go
Oh my god
You're insane
We're firing on all
With me so forty foot of that
If you want to capture and share your best plays with us
Download metal tv from our description and start recording
It's easy to use
And we want to see your epic plays
Oh moved by jet to push that smoke
They almost caught phoenix off guard
But that reaction time was too supreme
I'm good for three
Go get him buddy
One enemy remaining four
Do elijah
They're both there
Three three three
What one enemy remaining four out of five
Last player standing spike down b and a bait for the ace
What gun did he have found you gun here inside the clone
Why do you know
Twelve men
Thirty seconds left one enemy remaining
The fact that that breach had a shotgun there
Made things a lot scarier than they had to be
That was a good move to avoid getting concussed
Too
That's a
It was
You know
We have
Okay
You guys don't do it a bit
Ako came out of nowhere
They thought he was spawn
And then he just popped out kudos to the reaction time
Huh
Down from
Found one
I got this in the morning
They are standing
A a is
Wait
That's kind of crazy
I really want that vandal
You better
I'm at least gonna get a hell of a round enemy
Remaining four
She's hit eighty eight
Oh my god
Better you better you better you better you better
Hold them to their grave
Reeling them in
Something off your feet
How they hit that is beyond me
It was a headshot
Too breach has to be so tilted
Considering deadlock didn't even have time to plant anymore
You know what
The  were people of all
Spike down b
Got three one enemy remaining
That's not good so far
When i'm not aware
I know you well
One enemy remaining
There's nothing quite like clutching up in a one v five on pistol round
Especially as a sage player
It makes everyone want to step up their game
A player standing
I've never seen you lose the island board
I've never seen you do this
This is the kind of hopi could get behind
What is this call of duty
Every time i see quick scopes like that
It feels like a different game
Raise a lower local hill
One enemy remaining
I have never seen you do this
I was
I was cutting through
Yeah
Send five more
We can do this again
Rina really is a fantastic one v five agent
I mean the healing
And this can really help out when you're outnumbered right
One enemy reminds us down to the one v one
A whole new game begins
It's just you versus them
Only annoying part is figuring out where they're at
Give me my ov
You are the mother see
You know
I mean
What the hell
One enemy remaining song freckle
Watch them run
Cover going out
Got him
With crazy
Crazy
It's okay
It's crazy
He's left
Just push up
Push up
Run it down
You have
You have both you have both options
One enemy remaining
Oh that last shot on the
Oh my goodness
Players that are low hp and still go for crazy plays
Always have my respect
Thirty seconds left one enemy remaining
Bow before me
Last player standing
I'm so sorry
Bruh bike down a
Ah i see you so
Having the knife out when they came off the spike
Had me really nervous
But they recovered all is good
They won players standing
So where do we go got spike planted
Here comes
Oh yeah
Monster on the wait for me grenade
Like you could stop me
I've got your train nicely
Why do i feel like every split game devolves into a strange fight
Back here at this location
It's like in every game
I swear
One enemy remaining now
For nice revealing area come no
I didn't
I even left my neck off
Yeah
I'm sorry
Even when i realize also
I know i i i i i i saw
I only do
I understand why i used to
Three gone
One enemy remaining
Hey
I never said they had to win the round
They still won
V five
The enemy team
And that's what really matters at the end of the day
Yeah
I hope you
One enemy remaining ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Three killed one enemy remaining
Four dead
See nothing
Last player standing one enemy remaining ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
That i left
You know
I was not anticipating
And reina with the old pop to somehow win them
Their first round of the game
But here we are
My ot's ready
I told you they're all there
Okay
Come on clutch up
Clutch
I have this bike
Can't deny
One enemy remaining quadra and in for
That's three one enemy remaining
I can't believe they were able to hit so many of them
With a concussive ability
That had to be obnoxious for the enemy team to deal with
Especially while trapped in maine
Got three
My ultimate is ready
One enemy remaining
Got him
Enemy remaining
Well great game sense
But also fantastic use of the sound to wrap that one up
Hope you enjoyed the plays as much as we did
Hit that like subscribe and comment below
For a shot at the giveaway
And until next time have a great day
And i'll see you in the next one